nextshe.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy&Security Policy

**Introduction**

This site is operated by Nextshe. Nextshe protects the confidentiality of your personal information. If you have any concerns, questions or comments about this privacy statement or the website, please contact us through the email: [service@nextshe.com](mailto:service@nextshe.com).

**The types of personal information we collect and how we collect it**

● Information you provide upon registration: the use of specific services on the site, such as the forum and e-mail newsletters. We recommend that you register an account on our website. We will use your data in accordance with your instructions as set out in this privacy policy.  
   
 ● Information you order a product from us: When you place an order on Nextshe, you need to offer certain personal information so that the order can be fulfilled.  
   
 ● Information you enter a promotion or contest: If you participate in a promotion or contest, you must provide an account, or log some personal data used in accordance with the terms of the promotion or contest.

 ● Information you participate in any survey: If you participate in a survey or research, you have to provide an account or certain personal information to us with which we will use to meet the conditions of the survey and other data  
   
 ● Demographic and other data: This site uses cookies, Web Analytics and Web server logs to collect information about your use of our website, information about your computer's IP address, and browser type for demographic data collection, and the exact time you come to our site via a link from a third party site, the URL of the referring page. If you have registered an account, it may include your name and email address. The data through cookies, Web Analytics and Web logs are stored to transfer to third parties.

 ● E-mail communication: we use Web beacons in our e-mails to track the success of our marketing campaigns. If you open an e-mail from us, we can see which pages of our website you have visited. Our web beacons do not store data on your computer, but by communicating with our cookies on your computer, they can tell us if you open an e-mail from us. We may keep track of the emails that we sent to you. We also have a record of the communication that whether you have chosen to receive or not. If you want to opt out of receiving such e-mails, just click "unsubscribe" link.

**How we use the information we have collected**

We use the information collected as applicable to:

● We offer products you have ordered, such as newsletter subscriptions, order confirmation to execute from you about your registered account.

● Our rights to enforce and protect the safety of personal information, including the investigation and removal of any content that we receive a complaint on behalf of our group companies.

● If you do not want to receive such marketing information, you can mail us. You can use this information at any time by the instructions on the correspondence of any purpose. We are obliged by law or other regulatory or government agency at your service. 

**Who we share your personal information with**

● Agents: We perform certain functions on our behalf through third parties, including fulfilling orders, emails, organizing and managing events, promotions, surveys or polls, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Website analysis using data analysis and processing credit card payments with you. We may use your personal information if required, but we cannot use it for other purposes, unless their explicit permission.

● Aggregate Information: We may aggregate certain products or services through This website to put together with a third party available: non-personal information such as demographic information and use of the website statistics with advertisers, sponsors and other organizations.  
   
● Products or services in cooperation with the third parties: The third party may require your personal information in order to obtain  such products or services. If you ordered a product or service in conjunction with a third party, you will offer your personal information for  identity of third parties. The use of your personal information by that third party will follow the procedures of its privacy policies.

**Maintenance and storage of information**

Your information is collected and stored on servers maintained in the possession on behalf of Nextshe office. We may use your information  for a reasonable period obeyed its privacy policies.

**Links to other websites**

This website contains links to other websites. Despite these affiliate programs, we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites, even if the site logo as part of a co-branding agreement, nor for the way information is processed using their users. For personal information on such sites, you should check their privacy policy.

**Safety**

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent unauthorized access to your information. Neither Nextshe nor its affiliates are liable for attempting to hack or crack.

**Policy changes**

By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. We may amend and update Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions from time to time. You are bound by the revised terms of your continued use of this website.

**Questions about this site and the information we hold about you**

If you have general questions about this site or the way we collect and use your account information, you can contact us through the e-mail: [service@Nextshe.com.](mailto:service@nextshe.com)
